Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers ca. 1954-1992 MSS 092
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Manuscripts
  - Subseries A: Manuscripts
    - Zombie piece, undated (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Poetry-"History Keeps Me Awake Some Nights", undated (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Poetry/Prose-Poems, undated (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Poetry/Prose-Poems, undated (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - Poetry/Prose-Poems - with corrections, undated (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Poetry/Prose-Poems - handwritten, undated (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Poetry/Prose-Poems, undated (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Poetry/Prose-Poems, undated (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - Poetry/Prose-Poems - for Hujar, undated (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - Poetry/Prose-Poems, undated (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - Poetry/Prose-Poems, undated (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - Poetry/Prose-Poems - drafts, undated (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Poetry/Prose-Poems, undated (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Poetry/Prose-Poems, undated (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Poetry/Prose, undated (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - Poetry/Prose, undated (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - untitled mss. - for Brian, undated (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - untitled mss., undated (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - mss notes and fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Subseries B: Notebook Manuscripts
    - notebook-Tristan Tzara, Feb. 1978 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - notebook mss-3 Feb. 1978 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - notebook-France 1979 (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - notebook-1979 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - notebook mss-"Man Ray", undated (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - notebook mss-"Scenes for a Novel", undated (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - notebook/mss --- "Winged Snail", undated (Box 5, Folder 215A.)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 215B.)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 215C.)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 215D.)
    - notebooks/mss, undated (Box 5, Folder 215E.)
  - Subseries C: Lectures/Talks
    - Lecture notes and cards-Illinois State University, undated (Box 6, Folder 216)
    - Lecture-Illinois State University-three versions, undated (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - Lecture-Illinois State University-final version, undated (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - New American Radio Talk, undated (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Subseries D: Monologues
    - "Boy in Horn.", undated (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - "Boy in YMCA.", undated (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - "Canadian Trucker.", undated (Box 6, Folder 222)
    - "Coffeeshop After All These.", undated (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - "Guy on Second Ave."-with corrections, undated (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - "Guy on 14th St.", undated (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - "Guy in Music.", undated (Box 6, Folder 226)
    - "Guy Waiting.", undated (Box 6, Folder 227)
    - "Guy Wakes Up.", undated (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - "Guy in Waterfront Hotel", undated (Box 6, Folder 229)
    - "Hobo in Flatcar", undated (Box 6, Folder 230)
    - "Image, Eye and Mock", undated (Box 6, Folder 231)
    - "Interrogation", undated (Box 6, Folder 232)
    - "Indian Kid", undated (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - "Kentucky Trucker", undated (Box 6, Folder 234)
    - "Kiki on Ludlow.", undated (Box 6, Folder 235)
    - "The Listener", undated (Box 6, Folder 236)
    - "Man in Doorway", undated (Box 6, Folder 237)
    - "Man in Lower-East Side.", undated (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - "Man in Portland", undated (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - "Man in Sunshine.", undated (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - "Young Woman in Coffeeshop", undated (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - Subseries E: Booklength Monologues
    - Monologues from the Road, undated (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - Sounds in the Distance-cover art, undated (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - Sounds in the Distance-mss, undated (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - Sounds in the Distance-first set, 24pp, undated (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - Sounds in the Distance-first set, 52pp, undated (Box 6, Folder 246)
    - Sounds in the Distance-second set, undated (Box 6, Folder 247)
    - Sounds in the Distance-second set, 23pp, undated (Box 6, Folder 248)
    - Sounds in the Distance-Ed. by Rinaldi, undated (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - Sounds in the Distance-final mss, undated (Box 6, Folder 250)
    - Ten Monologues, undated (Box 6, Folder 251)
    - Monologues for Tom Rubnitz video, undated (Box 6, Folder 252)
    - Monologues for Tom Rubnitz video, undated (Box 6, Folder 253)
    - Monologues-misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 254)
    - Monologues-misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 255)
    - Monologues-misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - Monologues-misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 257)
    - Monologues-misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 258)
    - Monologues-misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - Subseries F: Scripts/Plays
    - The End-title pages, undated (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - Fear of Disclosure-script, undated (Box 6, Folder 261)
    - Fear of Disclosure--script, undated (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - Fear of Disclosure-tape transcript, undated (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - Fear of Disclosure-tape transcript, undated (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Fear of Disclosure-mss description for Gay Men's Health Crisis, undated (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - Fear of Disclosure-Image script, undated (Box 6, Folder 266)
    - Occicere-two act play, undated (Box 6, Folder 267)
    - Rimbaud in New York-film script, undated (Box 6, Folder 268)
    - Untitled script, undated (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Untitled script, undated (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - Untitled script, undated (Box 6, Folder 271)
    - Untitled script, fragment, undated (Box 6, Folder 272)
    - Film script notes for film adaptation of Burroughs' Wild Boys, undated (Box 6, Folder 273)
    - Film notes (removed from box F-3), undated (Box 6, Folder 274)
    - Film notes (removed from box F-7), undated (Box 6, Folder 275)
    - Film notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 276)
    - Film notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 277)
    - Performance notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 278)
  - Subseries G: Performance Collaborations
    - ITSOFOMO-script mock-ups (notes by Felix Guattari), undated (Box 6, Folder 279)
    - ITSOFOMO-script, unbound, undated (Box 6, Folder 280)
    - ITSOFOMO-script, unbound, undated (Box 6, Folder 281)
    - ITSOFOMO-"If I had a dollar.", undated (Box 6, Folder 282)
    - ITSOFOMO-Performance notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 283)
    - ITSOFOMO-Performance notes, two versions, undated (Box 6, Folder 284)
    - Seven Miles a Second-mock-ups, undated (Box 6, Folder 285)
    - Seven Miles a Second-mock-ups, undated (Box 6, Folder 286)
    - Seven Miles a Second-mock-ups, undated (Box 6, Folder 287)
    - Where Evil Dwells-Turner and Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 6, Folder 288)
  - Subseries H: Manuscripts by Others
    - Randy Atlas "Weapons Used in Prison", undated (Box 6, Folder 289)
    - Steve Brown "Rusty and Billy", undated (Box 6, Folder 290)
    - Gloria Bornstein "Don't Run from a Man Named Climax", undated (Box 6, Folder 290A.)
    - Ronnie Burk-mss in zine form unbound and edited, undated (Box 6, Folder 291)
    - William S. Burroughs endorsement, undated (Box 6, Folder 292)
    - William S. Burroughs "Burroughs on David Wojnarowicz's Art", undated (Box 6, Folder 293)
    - Brian Butterick-poem, undated (Box 6, Folder 294)
    - L. R. Cartwright "Confidence", undated (Box 6, Folder 295)
    - Katherine Dieckmann "Double Exposure", undated (Box 6, Folder 296)
    - Steve Doughton-untitled mss, undated (Box 6, Folder 297)
    - Luis Frangella file, undated (Box 6, Folder 298)
    - reviews of Ivan Galietti's Pompeii New York, undated (Box 6, Folder 299)
    - Griffy drawing, undated (Box 6, Folder 300)
    - Andy Grundberg "Photography's Lost Generation", undated (Box 6, Folder 301)
    - Felix Guattari on Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 6, Folder 302)
    - M. Houston and R. Kern "How Magic Works", undated (Box 6, Folder 302A.)
    - Peter Hujar-untitled mss, undated (Box 6, Folder 303)
    - Peter Hujar-untitled mss, monologue, undated (Box 6, Folder 304)
    - Jean Genet with the Black Panthers, undated (Box 7, Folder 305)
    - Kilpatrick, J. F. and A. G. Kilpatrick "Notebook of a Cherokee Shaman", undated (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - William Loomis "Happy Happy.", undated (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - Lydia Lunch Incriminating Evidence, undated (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - Douglas MacCash "David Wojnarowicz at this Distance", undated (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - Steve McLean Postcards from America, undated (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - Steve McLean Postcards from America-final bound version, undated (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - Charles Mee "Imperialists at the Club Cave", undated (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - T. C. Morrison-correspondence and mss, undated (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - Poems-unidentified author, undated (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - Tom Rauffenbart-dream log, undated (Box 7, Folder 315)
    - K. Robert Schwarz "Playing (and Singing) Politics", undated (Box 7, Folder 316)
    - Serpent's Tail promotional material and Shopping in Space mss, undated (Box 7, Folder 317)
    - Patti Smith poster, undated (Box 7, Folder 318)
    - Paul Thek "Teaching Notes: 4 Dimensional Design", undated (Box 7, Folder 318A.)
    - Dhoruba Bin Wahad "The U. S. War Against the Black Panther Party", undated (Box 7, Folder 319)
    - Richard Woodward "All the Rage, Posthumously", undated (Box 7, Folder 320)
    - unidentified mss. 'The Death Bird", undated (Box 7, Folder 321)
    - .Extra folder "An Attempt to Define.", undated (Box 7, Folder 322)
- Series IV: Phone Logs
  Scope and Content note
  Folders in Series IV: Phone Logs may also contain manuscripts, sketches etc.
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Phone log, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Phone book, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Series V: Art Magazines and Catalogue Contributions
  - Subseries A: Contributions of Artwork to Art Magazines by Wojnarowicz
    - Architectural Digest, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Art in America July, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Artforum Summer 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Artforum Sept. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Contemporary Art Contemporanea magazine November, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Horizon December, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Maandblad, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - New Yorker, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Spin, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Subseries B: Articles by Wojnarowicz
    - Wojnarowicz "Spiral", undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Wojnarowicz "Being Queer in America", undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Wojnarowicz "Losing the Form in Darkness", undated (Box 8, Folder 11A.)
    - Wojnarowicz with Doug Bressler "American Dreamtime", undated (Box 8, Folder 11B.)
    - Wojnarowicz "Man in Dark Sunglasses by the Silver Arc", undated (Box 8, Folder 11C.)
  - Subseries C: Articles on Wojnarowicz in Art Magazines
    - LD Berghtol, "In My Life," HX June, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11E.)
    - Cindy Carr "Portrait of the Artist", undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Cindy Carr "Troubleshooters" Artforum September, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Lawrence Chua "David Wojnarowicz", undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Cone, Timothy "Art and the Law", undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - David Deitcher "Ideas and Emotions", undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - John Donahue "Flower Power", undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Mark Alice Durant "Sustained Rage in a Hostile Landscape", undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Brigitte Engler "Peinture et Guerre Civile", undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - David Finkle "Postcards from America", undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Jurgen Fischer "Neue Heimat", undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Nichols Fox "NEA", undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Stephen Hager "From Street to Salon with David.", undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Howard Hampton "Public Enemies" Artforum, April, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Elizabeth Hess "Queer in Normal", undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Joe Jarrell "God is in the Details", undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Koch, Stephen "Warhol", undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Eric Latzky "Lip Service", undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Lucy Lippard "Out of the Safety Zone", undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Carlo McCormick "High Art", undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - MOMA "Gathering Hope", undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Allan Parachini "Fighting Back", undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Stephen Perloff "A Censorship Diary", undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Sarah Pettit "The Arts", undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Howardena Pindella "Breaking the Silence", undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - . Out, Issue 1, Summer 1992 (Box 8, Folder 35 A.)
    - Calvin Reid "Beyond Mourning", undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Matthew Rose "David Wojnarowicz", undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - David Rubin "Primary Structures", undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Jerry Saltz "Not Going Gentle", undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Peter Schjeldahl "Life Equals Noise", undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - K. Schwartz "Continental.", undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Frank Wagner "David Wojnarowicz", undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Frank Wagner "Ubers Sofa!", undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Michelle Wallace "The Cave", undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Linda Yablonskaya "Covering the Slaughterfront", undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Subseries D: Misc. Articles and Mentions
    [see also Flat Box]
    - David Joselit "Power of Portraitist" [on Peter Hujar], undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Frank Graziano "Alejandra Pizarnik", undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Mention-"High and Low.", undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Mention-"The Neo-Dealers", undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Mention-"Planet Ludlow", undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Mention-"Woman Behaving Badly", undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Mention --- "Rough Draft of Journal Entries from the Sur Rodney Diary" [on Keith Davis], undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Mention-"Diane Plays Ball; Katie Plays for Laughs." Premiere Magazine., undated (Box 8, Folder 52A.)
    - Mention-"On the Waterfront" Out Magazine, 10/1997. (Box 8, Folder 52B.)
    - Mention-"A Living Testament of Blood Fairies: Part II" Art in America. 4/1997 (Box 8, Folder 52C.)
    - Mention-Art in America, 11/1994 (Box 8, Folder 53D.)
    - C. Carr, Samuel R. Delany, James A. Baggett "Born in Flames", undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Peter Walsh "Call of the Wild", undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Mention --- "Simon Says", undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Michael Kimmelman "Art Club", undated (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Mention --- "The Aids Decade", undated (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Mention --- "Mix" ("One"), undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Herbert Reichert "Life & Death", undated (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Bill Arning " 'Fever' Dreams" (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Peter Von Ziegesar "(David) Wojnarowicz", undated (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Walter Robinson "Stray Genius", undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Mention --- Jerome Charyn, "Metropolis", undated (Box 9, Folder 62A.)
    - Mention --- "David Wojnarowicz Feature", undated (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Mention --- "An Artist with a Beef", undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Series VI: Biographical
  - Subseries A: Photographs
    - Art agreements, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Biographical dateline, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Bio-Wojnarowicz family, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Consent forms, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Illinois State University exhibition-checklist of works, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Medical-American Hospitals of Paris test results, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Medical-HIV study report: informed consent, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Medical-morphine document, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Insurance-medical and art, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Photos, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Photos, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Photos, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Photos, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Photos (color Xerox), undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Photos (print) - Hujar, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Prize, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Subseries B: Obituaries
    - Announcement of memorial, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Funeral log, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Obituary, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Obituary-Art in America, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Obituary-City of LA, "In Tribute", undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Obituary-Entertainment Weekly, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Obituary-Entertainment Weekly, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Obituary-Interzone Vogue, dedicated to Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Obituary-New Art Examiner, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Obituary-NY Newsday, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Obituary-NY Times, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Obituary-NY Times, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Obituary-Newsweek, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Obituary-Otherside, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Obituary-OUT, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Obituary-Paper Sept. 1992 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Obituary-People, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Obituary-QW, "Fighting Words", undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Obituary-Review, "City of Widows", undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Obituary-Review, "Notes on the Blood-Filled Egg", undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Obituary-Review, "Stonewalled at the Museum", undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Obituary-TIME June 1990 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Obituary-TIME August 1992 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Obituary-tribute/memorial program, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Tom's notes for memorial service, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Subseries C: Reviews
    - Articles re: AIDS protest against FDA, undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Mention, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Misc. Articles/reviews/commentary/reflections, undated (Box 9, Folder 55 A.)
    - Review, undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Review - p. 133, undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Review, undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Review-AIDS exhibit, Switzerland, undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Review-art and flyer, undated (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Review-Artforum tear sheets for Gracie Mansion Gallery, undated (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Review-Arts Magazine tearsheets, undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Review-Carr, C. Village Voice, undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Review-Close to the Knives, undated (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Review-Close to the Knives, undated (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Review-Close to the Knives & Memories; That Smell & letter from Serpent's Tail (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Review-critical piece on Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Review-Gracie Mansion Gallery, undated (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Review-Gracie Mansion review material, undated (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Review --- "In the Shadow of the American Dream", undated (Box 10, Folder 69A.)
    - Review-Memories That Smell Like Gasoline, Out, Summer, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Review-misc., undated (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Reviews --- various exhibitions, installations, performances, undated (Box 10, Folder 71A.)
    - Reviews --- various exhibitions and publications, undated (Box 10, Folder 71B.)
    - Review-Mueller, C. "Art and About", undated (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Review-Postcards from America, undated (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Review --- Postcards from America, undated (Box 10, Folder 73A.)
    - Review-Rimbaud, undated (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Review-"7 Miles a Second", undated (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Review-"7 Miles a Second", undated (Box 10, Folder 75A.)
    - Review-"7 Miles a Second", undated (Box 10, Folder 75B.)
    - Review-"7 Miles a Second", undated (Box 10, Folder 75C.)